Naeem Ullah Khan

Full Stack Developer

+49 1520 7468655

% https://naeemkhan.dev

I am a full stack developer with approximately two years of industry experience, proficient in various front-end and back-end technologies. Currently, I am pursuing a Master's degree in Computer Science with a focus on cyber security, aiming to expand my knowledge and gain valuable experience in the industry.

Work experience

01/2022 - 01/2023

Full Stack Developer

Archirodon Construction (Overseas) Company Limited Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates

Tech Stack: Python, Typescript, PostgreSQL, Microsoft Azure.

- Designed and developed a full-stack application using Django Rest Framework serving as the back-end REST API endpoint, and designed front-end components using Angular, with PostgreSQL used as the database.
- Implemented different testing strategies such as unit testing, end-to-end testing, integration testing using Factory Boy + Faker for Django, and Jasmine/Karma for Angular.

10/2021 - 12/2021

Software Developer Internship

Archirodon Construction (Overseas) Company Limited Dubai, United Arab Emirates

• Gathered project requirements and created a low-fidelity prototype for a custom ERP application for the company.

05/2019 -

08/2019

Junior Software Developer Internship

Chartercross Capital Management Dubai, United Arab Emirates

- Worked on multiple projects involving back-end and front-end web development using PHP and Python.
- Learned different frameworks, revamped different projects and helped train the new interns.

Education

04/2023

MSc: Computer Science (Cyber Security)

SRH Berlin University of Applied Sciences Berlin, Germany

09/2017 -

BSc: Computer Science

07/2021

Heriot-Watt University Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Programing Languages Python

Expert

Typescript/Javascript

Intermediate

SQL

Intermediate **HTML/CSS**

Expert

Libraries/Frameworks

Django/Django Rest Framework (DRF)

Expert

Expert **Angular**

Intermediate

Tailwind

Expert **Bootstrap**

Intermediate

Hobbies

Astrophotography

Gaming

Anime

Databases (DBMS)

PostgreSQL

Expert

MySQL

Intermediate

MongoDB

Beginner

Skills

Linux Git

Docker

Kubernetes

CI/CD

Microsoft Office

MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint.

Languages

English

Fluent (C1)

Urdu

Native